thegabrielmethod.com 2017-02-14

# The Gabriel Method – Privacy Policy

At The Gabriel Method, we care about your privacy. This policy describes how we will deal with your personal information in accordance with the National Privacy Principles and the Australian Privacy Act.

**What is Personal Information?**

When we talk about **personal information** , we mean information or an opinion about an individual where you can tell or reasonably work out who the information or opinion is about.

**Getting to know you**

To help us help you, it is often important we know a few things about you. However, we will only collect personal information about you that is relevant to our relationship.

Where reasonably possible, we will only collect personal information when you know we are. For example, we may request general information like your name, e-mail address and contact details when you ask us a question or contact us. We may also need to ask for other information, including your credit card details, shipping address and computer’s IP address when you wish to purchase a product or a service from us. If you do not provide some of this information, we may not be able to fulfill your request.

Some sections of our website, such as our forums, allow you to store and publish personal information about you and other people. You are responsible and accept liability for ensuring that those people are happy to have their personal information published on this site and are made aware of the terms of this privacy policy. You authorise us to contact any third person to confirm that they are happy for their personal information to be posted here, but we are under no obligation to you to do so.

Our purpose for collecting personal information should be clear when we collect it. If you are not sure, please contact us by email, or write to us at the address below.

You can generally visit our website without revealing who you are or other personal information. We will not collect any personal information about you when you visit our website except where you are a registered member, or where you knowingly provide us with personal information.

We may keep track of which sections of our website you visit for internal purposes, including to help us improve our website and other services.

**Use and disclosure**

Subject to our legal obligations and our other rights under any agreement with you, we will do our best to only give out your personal information to those people listed below and to any other people you have asked us to provide it to.

We will only use your personal information as allowed by law. This means we may use it for the purpose it was collected, as apparent at the time of collection, or as otherwise set out in this policy. If we want to use your information for any other purpose, we will first seek your consent unless we are not required to by law.

We generally only use or disclose your personal information to:

  1. provide you with information, products or services you have requested;
  2. promote your success story to visitors to our website through testimonial or other feedback pages with your consent;
  3. help us to improve our website, marketing and services;
  4. tell you about any new developments, offers or events we think may interest you;
  5. other organisations that provide services to us, such as mailing houses, event organisers, IT contractors (such as website developers and hosts), internet service providers and professional services firms;
  6. credit reference and reporting agencies and other credit providers if you place a large order or wish us to extend credit;
  7. law enforcement and other government agencies where permitted by law; and
  8. meet any legal requirements.

While we strive to protect and respect your privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you send over the Internet. When you post information on a section of our site available to others, such as in our forums, it becomes available to all other visitors to that section of our site.

**Access to personal information**

You can request access to personal information we hold about you at any time. We will give you access unless we are allowed or required by law to refuse it. We may ask you to pay our reasonable costs of providing access.

If you believe personal information we hold about you is inaccurate or incomplete, please let us know. We will generally take reasonable steps to correct your personal information where inaccuracies are found.

In certain circumstances, we may refuse to give access to your personal information or amend it. Usually we will explain why and, in the case of an amendment, make a note that you disagree with the accuracy or completeness of particular information.

**Security and integrity**

We cannot guarantee the security of information you may transmit to us. We will take reasonable steps to keep your personal information secure, accurate, complete and up to date except where at the time you supply it, it is clear that it will be published on the website. If we no longer require your personal information, we will take reasonable steps to destroy or de-identify it. We do not take responsibility for the security of information that is outside our control such as when it is sent over the Internet.

**Changes to this policy**

To keep up with regulatory, technical and organisational change, we may change this policy from time to time by publishing the updated policy on our website. Please be sure to visit our website regularly to keep up to date with any changes.
